A movie about empowering women (the hot ones).
Bottoms is a comedy film directed by Emma Seligman.
Unpopular best friends PJ and Josie start a high school
self-defense club to meet girls and lose their virginity.
They soon find themselves in over their heads when the most popular
students start beating each other up in the name of self-defense.
PJ, played by Rachel Sennott.
Josie, played by Ayo Edebiri.
Hazel Callahan, played by Ruby Cruz.
Isabel, played by Havana Rose Liu.
Brittany, played by Kaia Gerber.
Jeff, played by Nicholas Galitzine.
Bottoms is a 2023 American satirical black comedy film directed by
Emma Seligman, who co-wrote it with Rachel Sennott.
The film stars Sennott, Ayo Edebiri, Ruby Cruz in her feature film debut, Havana Rose Liu, Kaia
Gerber, Nicholas Galitzine, Miles Fowler, Dagmara Domińczyk, and Marshawn Lynch.
The plot follows two high school senior girls who start a
fight club as a way to hook up with cheerleaders.
Bottoms premiered at South by Southwest on March 11, 2023, and was released in
the United States on August 25, by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures.
The film received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of high school, cheerleader,
female friendship, bullying, coming of age.
The tone is lighthearted.